<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fingineering.net - Data Engineering at it&#39;s best</title>
    <link>https://fingineering.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Fingineering.net - Data Engineering at it&#39;s best</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fingineering.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Download original template</title>
      <link>https://fingineering.net/home/downloads/download1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fingineering.net/home/downloads/download1/</guid>
      <description>A simple, nice-looking call to action box. Boxing is about respect. getting it for yourself, and taking it away from the other guy. no, this is mount everest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://fingineering.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fingineering.net/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi I&amp;rsquo;m Otrek, an engineer, software developer, and project manager, who loves to create solutions, learn new things, and is always open to a good challenge. For more than 14 years I&amp;rsquo;m always involved in some kind of software development project related to the analysis and management of data.
I started my career as a vehicle engineering student at TU-Berlin but realized that HPC Software development is my go-to task pretty quick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Datenschutzerklärung</title>
      <link>https://fingineering.net/datenschutz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fingineering.net/datenschutz/</guid>
      <description>Datenschutzerklärung Einführung Der Schutz Ihrer Privatsphäre und Ihrer persönlichen Daten ist uns wichtig. Deshalb informieren wir Sie in der nachfolgenden Datenschutzerklärung gemäß den gesetzlichen Vorgaben (insb. gemäß BDSG n.F. und der europäischen Datenschutz-Grundverordnung ‚DS-GVO‘) über die Art, den Umfang und Zweck der Verarbeitung personenbezogener Daten durch unser Unternehmen. Diese Datenschutzerklärung gilt auch für unsere Websites und Sozial-Media-Profile. Bezüglich der Definition von Begriffen wie etwa „personenbezogene Daten“ oder „Verarbeitung“ verweisen wir auf Art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impressum</title>
      <link>https://fingineering.net/impressum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fingineering.net/impressum/</guid>
      <description>Impressum Geschäftsführer: Otrek Wilke
Ust-IdNr.: DE340355201</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science</title>
      <link>https://fingineering.net/home/services/service3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fingineering.net/home/services/service3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Now that you have your data in one place and connected your services via your data logistics platform, leverage your data to make better decisions. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journey to the Cloud</title>
      <link>https://fingineering.net/home/services/service2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fingineering.net/home/services/service2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Running a business on-premise can slow down development and create uneccessary costs. Start your journey to the cloud today and follow these three steps.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Engineering</title>
      <link>https://fingineering.net/home/services/service1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fingineering.net/home/services/service1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Do you know that feeling, when you have to manually copy information from one
system to another? A Data Logistics Platform can make that go away! Enter data
once, generate Information everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The first webpage with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://fingineering.net/post/the-first-internal-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fingineering.net/post/the-first-internal-blog/</guid>
      <description>Creating a personal portfolio web page was on my list for 2021, after a first attempt using Google Pages - nice but very limited - and a second attempt using WordPress - which never came out of testing and fiddling around - this is how I&amp;rsquo;ll move on. Creating a static web page using Hugo.
Why? Well, why, obvious - a place to share with you: services that I have on offer, information and tutorials that you might find useful and to give you a place to find me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fingineering.net/home/subheader/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fingineering.net/home/subheader/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to fingineering.net here you find solutions based on data. I&amp;rsquo;ll help you to get control over your data and generate insight and knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download HUGO template</title>
      <link>https://fingineering.net/home/downloads/download2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fingineering.net/home/downloads/download2/</guid>
      <description>Another simple, nice-looking call to action box. Boxing is about respect. getting it for yourself, and taking it away from the other guy. no, this is mount everest.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
